<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>aeternity aepps Portal</title>
    <link>https://www.aepps.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on aeternity aepps Portal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 19:55:18 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.aepps.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Imprint</title>
      <link>https://www.aepps.com/imprint/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 19:55:18 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aepps.com/imprint/</guid>
      <description>Aeternity Establishment  Landstr. 123 FL-9495 Triesen info@aeternity.com PEID / Steuernummer: 2528358 Hinweise zum Datenschutz Ihr Vertrauen ist uns wichtig. Deshalb respektieren wir den Datenschutz und informieren Sie über die erhobenen und gespeicherten Daten und Ihre Rechte auf Auskunft, Berichtigung, Sperrung und Löschung.
1. Datenerhebung und -speicherung Wenn eine Webseite besucht wird, sendet der Browser grundsätzlich Informationen über Browsertyp und Browserversion, das verwandte Betriebssystem, die Referrer-URL, die IP-Adresse, den Dateinamen, den Zugriffsstatus, die übertragene Datenmenge, das Datum und die Uhrzeit der Serveranfrage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to get started with Aeternity development</title>
      <link>https://www.aepps.com/get-started-with-ae/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 19:49:51 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aepps.com/get-started-with-ae/</guid>
      <description>Here are some steps you can follow to get going with Aeternity aepp development. The goal is to built an app (we call them aepps) which will
 Use AE test tokens for transactions or signing Use the identity manager to easily approve these actions  We run the aepps in the Ethereum Kovan network. So for write actions to this blockchain Gas in the form of Kovan-ETH tokens (KETH) will be needed and we won’t transfer real AE tokens, though Kovan-AE tokens (KAE).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Test Aepp</title>
      <link>https://www.aepps.com/hackathon-aepps/test/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 18:34:33 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.aepps.com/hackathon-aepps/test/</guid>
      <description>About the aepp Which problem is your æpp solving?
Dolor natus modi ipsum tempore quod, ipsam Eius neque delectus dolor explicabo architecto Aperiam inventore dicta quas at asperiores sit What was your approach?
Sit dolore nesciunt veniam commodi eum Repudiandae quia accusantium officiis doloribus sed. Facilis ea et ipsum adipisci quidem Eligendi facere nesciunt blanditiis voluptas alias odit? Eaque cupiditate sed dolor rerum quibusdam consectetur repellat Nobis et earum facilis maiores voluptate, architecto.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>